Mehmet Başaran

mehmet94nto@gmail.com | https://github.com/nto4/ | https://mehmetbasaran.me

05313803779 | Ankara/Turkey

Summary

I am a fourth-year student at Gazi University. I like to learn new technologies, best practices. I want to work part-time to gain experience and write better code and adapt to the sector by taking part in different projects. I have experience on c#, js ,python and I was work on .net, .net mvc, .net core and django, im familiar linux systems, testing and qa process also im familiar ml&dl using common librarys and api. I want to work with experienced programmers, and I think I will improve myself faster and more accurately with their guidance.

Education

- · Gazi University Computer Engineering Department 4. year.
- I was participated Linux 1, linux 1,5, network management -2 courses in LKD summer and winter camps

Employment

- · Angular front-end junior developer 3/2019-5/2019 (project based freelance)
- · Asp.net core mvc and angularjs junior software developer 6/2019- 10/2019 handson P.I. Works
- · Systems Support Specialist 7/2020-9/2020 Profelis Bilişim

Skills

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- · C# asp.net mvc& asp.net mvc core
- · Python and django rest
- · Object oriented programing & Functional programming
- · JavaScript, es6

SECONDARY LANGUAGES

- · Shell (bash, powershell)
- · Sql DDL &DML
- Python scripting

OTHER SKILS & FAMILIAR CONCEPTS AND FRAMEWORKS

- · Gnu/Linux familiar forme; centos, redhat and debian
- Experienced on Mysql, Sqlite and Postgresql 1 can write DDL & DML querys
- · Testing, Quality Assurance
- · Machine Learning & Deep learning using scikit learn, tensorflow, keras, pandas, numpy, Spyder

CERTIFICATES

· LE-1: Linux Essentials

https://cs.lpi.org/caf/Xamman/certification/verify/LPI000460851/7y4apbwguz